export const questions2 = [
  {
    question: 'Which space mission was the first to land a man on the Moon?',
    options: ['Apollo 13', 'Apollo 11', 'Apollo 8', 'Gemini 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Apollo 11',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which spacecraft was the first to leave the Solar System?',
    options: ['Voyager 1', 'Pioneer 10', 'New Horizons', 'Galileo'],
    correctAnswer: 'Voyager 1',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which space station was the first international space station?',
    options: ['Skylab', 'Mir', 'International Space Station (ISS)', 'Salyut 1'],
    correctAnswer: 'International Space Station (ISS)',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which space telescope is known for its deep space images?',
    options: ['Hubble', 'Kepler', 'Chandra', 'Spitzer'],
    correctAnswer: 'Hubble',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which mission explored the dwarf planet Pluto?',
    options: ['Dawn', 'Cassini', 'Juno', 'New Horizons'],
    correctAnswer: 'New Horizons',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which spacecraft landed on comet 67P/Churyumov-Gerasimenko?',
    options: ['Rosetta', 'Galileo', 'Hayabusa', 'Deep Impact'],
    correctAnswer: 'Rosetta',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which mission was the first to study Jupiter and its moons from orbit?',
    options: ['Juno', 'Galileo', 'Cassini', 'Voyager 2'],
    correctAnswer: 'Galileo',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which rover was the first to successfully land on Mars and explore its surface?',
    options: ['Spirit', 'Sojourner', 'Opportunity', 'Curiosity'],
    correctAnswer: 'Sojourner',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which mission explored the rings and moons of Saturn?',
    options: ['Cassini', 'Voyager 2', 'New Horizons', 'Mariner 10'],
    correctAnswer: 'Cassini',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which mission made the first soft landing on the far side of the Moon?',
    options: ['Luna 9', 'Surveyor 1', 'Chandrayaan-2', "Chang'e 4"],
    correctAnswer: "Chang'e 4",
  },
];
